# CONRAD TAKASHI

## ML | AI | EVM Engineer

https://www.catloverdev.com/

**+**1 313 742 3660

takashi75926@gmail.com

Oslo



## **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

#### **Hokkaido University**

**=** 04/2015 - 2019

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Tech Lead

#### Wizard-Tech

**Emotional AI Company** 

- · Lead and Integrate whole project: analysis of emotion from words, speech, tone, pose, face of customers and offer tailord advice based on LLM/CNN model.
- It consists of several parts such as speech-to-text transfer, detect emotion from speech, words, pose, face, offering tailored advice based on LLM, CNN and text-to-speech transfer.
- Building LLM model based on analysis of emotion and BERT. It offers tailored advice by text.
- Building CNN model based on analysis of emotion. It offers tailored advice by image.

## ML | AI | EVM Engineer

#### Anbudstoraet.no

**m** 03/2022 - 10/2023 Oslo

Agency Company

- Computer vision projects: Tennis ball tracking project using YOLOv8, Thyroid cancer diagnosis project from DICOM by CNN, Face clustering project using K-Means so on.
- NLP projects: Customized AI chatbot using LangChain, Fine-tuning LLM models such as BERT, GPT, T5, Building LLM models for question-answer system to provide legal advices.
- Forecasting projects: Stock marketing price prediction project using LSTM, Cryptocurrency price prediction using XGBoost, Sales amount prediction using SARIMA.
- EVM smart contract projects: Ethereum mint contract site, EVM smart contract development.

### ML | Al Engineer

### **Soundsensing**

**ਜ਼** 01/2021 - 12/2021 **♀** Oslo

Offering service based on ananlysis of speech in building

- Build and training of a deep reinforcement learning model to identify irregularities in speech patterns
- NLP for understanding speech and offering customized service.
- Integration deep learning model with Android and connecting speech sensor with deep learning model.

## **SUMMARY**

A ML | AI | EVM Engineer with rich experience in Computer Vision(CNN, OpenCV), NLP(OpenAI, LLM, OpenAI, LangChain), Time Series Forcasting(RNN, LSTM, GRU), Backend **Development**(Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB) and EVM smart contract / web3. Have interest in Combination of Blockchain and Al.

Capable of excelling as part of a team or individually in a fast-paced environment.

## **SKILLS**

AI | ML | DL

Blockchain | EVM | Solidity | Ether.js

Tensorflow | PyTorch | Keras

Python | JavaScript | TypeScript

NLP | LLM | OpenAI | LangChain

CV | CNN | OpenCV

ChromaDB | Weaviate | Pinecone

Numpy | Scipy | Pandas | Selenium

Node.js | Express.js | Django

## **EXPERIENCE**

## ML | Al Engineer

### **Precise Prediction Team**

Interactive visualizations and graphical analyses

- Built a prediction model using past business data / rules and it offered recommendations to customer critical business process.
- Built real-time capture system using webscrapping and analyze captured data to offer insight of data.
- Explored customer's data interactively and visualized streaming data. Created interactive dashboards with drill-down capabilities for business users.

Powered by Shancy